[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":110918,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":143275,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":18494,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":161773,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":31959,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":193734,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":6539,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":200275,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":9124,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":209401,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1774,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":211177,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get yo ur resul t.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":7020,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":218199,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":2116,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":220316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":8225,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":228541,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1  = 2 beca use 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":2134,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":230677,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6943,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":237621,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1389,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":239011,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with t he first  number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3880,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":242891,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1755,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":244649,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4485,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":249136,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":4006,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":253143,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4247,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":257391,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":2837,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":260230,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4213,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":264444,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1838,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":266283,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger,  you subt ract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3295,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":269580,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1394,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":270977,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":39171,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":310152,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":46295,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":356448,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":10516,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":366966,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":6548,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":373516,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":5926,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":379444,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2836,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":382282,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is th e invers e of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4790,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":387074,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4828,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":391904,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":5429,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":397334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2598,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":399934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":8122,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":408058,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":23425,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":431485,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":32827,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":464313,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <b r /><br  /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":66380,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":530694,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":21023,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":551720,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":39550,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":591272,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":47835,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":639107,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":12772,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":651880,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generat or under  +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":10178,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":662061,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":4867,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":666930,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":9031,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":675962,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":10459,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":686423,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the rem aining q uestions as accurately as possible.","rt":20594,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":707018,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":7998,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":715018,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1550,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":716570,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6102,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":722674,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"fr ee","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4477,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":727152,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3494,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":730649,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4758,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":735408,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6940,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":742350,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Four plus 1 is five which is less than +9 so the answer stays the same of five","response_history":["Four plusa","Four plus 1 is 5","Four plus 1 is five which is les t","Four plus 1 is five which is les ","Four plus 1 is five which is less than +9 so the answer stays the same of five"],"rt":51903,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":794254,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Eight plus four is 12 which is greater than +9 so you subtract nine from twelve and arrive at your answer of three","response_history":["Eight plus four is 12 which is ge","Eight plus  four is  12 which is greater than +9 so you subtract 12","Eight plus four is 12 which is greater than +9 so you subtract 1","Eight plus four is 12 which is greater than +9 so you subtract twelve from ","Eight plus four is 12 which is greater than +9 so you subtract t","Eight plus four is 12 which is greater than +9 so you subtract nine from twelve and arrive at your answer of three"],"rt":48179,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":842434,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"Zero because when combined with anything else you get the same number back","response_history":["Zero because when combined with anything else you get the same number back"],"rt":91968,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":934403,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.1 2-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"Four is the inverse of five because when you add five plus four you get nine and nine minues +9 is zero","response_history":["Four is the inverse of five because when you add five plus four you fet","Four is the inverse of five because when you add five plus four you fe","Four is the inverse of five because when you add five plus four you f","Four is the inverse of five because when you add five plus four you get 9","Four is the inverse of five because when you add five plus four you get nine and nine minues +9 iu","Four is the inverse of five because when you add five plus four you get nine and nine minues +9 is zero"],"rt":71405,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1005820,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":10028,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1015850,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":36394,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1052246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"six is the inverse because you add up and get 9 and then subtract 9 and get zero","response_history":["six is the inverse because you add up and get 9 and then subtract 9 and get zero"],"rt":27665,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1079913,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no because there is no way to make all the numbers just using 2?","response_history":["no bea","no becasues","no becasue","no becasu","no becas","no because there is no way to make all the numbers just using 2?"],"rt":76404,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1156318,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes because you can make the numbers under 9 with three","response_history":["Yes because you can make the numbers under 8 with th","Yes because you can make the numbers under 8 with t","Yes because you can make the numbers under 8 with ","Yes because you can make the numbers under 8  with"," Yes because you can make the numbers under 8 wit","Yes because you can make the numbers under 8 wi","Yes because you can make the numbers under 8 w","Yes because you can make the numbers under 8 ","Yes because you can make the numbers under 8","Yes because you can make the numbers under 9 with three"],"rt":101353,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1257673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No because you cannot make all the numbers with just 5","response_history":["No because you cannot b","No because you cannot nm","No because you cannot n","No because you cannot make all the b","No because you cannot make all the numbers with just 5"],"rt":26270,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1283944,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No it is too high to make all the numbers","response_history":["No it is too high to make all the bu","No it is too high to make all the b","No it is too high to make all the numbers"],"rt":24935,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1308881,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":38675,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1347558,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What  is the f ormula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+1+n=0","response_history":["1+1+n=0"],"rt":68666,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1416226,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"The inverse of 1+8+n=0 the inverse of x is 1 and +n is 9","response_history":["The inverse of 1+8+9=0","The inverse of 1+8+=0","The inverse of 1+8+n=0 the inverse of x is 1 and +n is 9"],"rt":86931,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1503158,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whe ther it  can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I am not sure, I would guess you just count in your head?","response_history":["I am sn","I am s","I am not sure, I would u","I am not sure, I would guess you just count in your head?"],"rt":34283,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1537443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":8947,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1546391,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":6248,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1552640,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":7476,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1560117,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"True, if x is not a generator than is must be a multiple of x and a divisor of n","response_history":["True, if x is not a generator thank","True, if x is not a generator tha n is muy ","True, if x is not a generator than is must be a multiple of xz","True, if x is not a generator than is must be a multiple of x and a divosor of n","True, if x is not a generator than is must be a multiple of x and a divsor of n","True, if x is not a generator than is must be a multiple of x and a divisor of n"],"rt":81289,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1641408,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":7966,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1649375,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</s ub> alwa ys, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Sometimes? Depends on the number you are looking at.","response_history":["Sometimes? Depends on the number you are looking at."],"rt":47230,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1696606,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":15064,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1711670,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":2847,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1714518,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"45","response_history":["45"],"rt":3248,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1717766,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":4142,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1721908,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you hav e multip le classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Wow it's been a while I would say geometry in high school, maybe algebra, I honestly do not remember, but I remember taking those classes though.","response_history":["Wow it's been a while I would say geometry in high school, maybe algebra, I honestly do not remember, but I remember taking those classes. I used to be really good in math","Wow it's been a while I would say geometry in high school, maybe algebra, I honestly do not remember, but I remember taking those classes though."],"rt":58080,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1779989,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or ex plained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":7927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1787917,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":7967,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1795885,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something  from thi s HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":6815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1802701,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":5990,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1808692,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3536,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1812229,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Female","response_history":["Female"],"rt":2359,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1814589,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":7711,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1822301,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":5399,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1827700,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Thanks for the study, my brain started to go dead once the numbers were lost, I feel like if I had more practice I might have done better in the later part. I am an extreme visual learner, so it was a bit more difficult having to read over seeing someone actually show me in person. ","response_history":["Thanks for the stuf","Thanks for the study, my brain started to go d","Thanks for the study, my brain started to go dead once the bn","Thanks for the study, my brain started to go dead once the b","Thanks for the study, my brain started to go dead once the numbers were lost, I feel like if I had more practive","Thanks for the study, my brain started to go dead once the numbers were lost, I feel like if I had more practiv","Thanks for the study, my brain started to go dead once the numbers were lost, I feel like if I had more  practiv","Thanks for the study, my brain started to go dead once the numbers were lost, I feel like if I had more practice I might have done better in the later part. I am an extreme vu","Thanks for the study, my brain started to go dead once the numbers were lost, I feel like if I had more practice I might have done better in the later part. I am an extreme visual learner, so it was a bit more difficult have ","Thanks for the study, my brain started to go dead once the numbers were lost, I feel like if I had more practice I might have done better in the later part. I am an extreme visual learner, so it was a bit more difficult have","Thanks for the study, my brain started to go dead once the numbers were lost, I feel like if I had more practice I might have done better in the later part. I am an extreme visual learner, so it was a bit more difficult having to read over seeing someone actually show me in person. "],"rt":89064,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1916765,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]